我昨晚没睡好  醒来之后嗓子很疼
I didn't sleep well last night, and I woke up with a scratchy throat.
我就是不太舒服  咳嗽
I just don't feel so good. Uh, cough.
我的胃也不太舒服  我觉得我发烧了
I have a bit of an upset stomach too, and I think I'm running a fever.
我怕这个会传染
I'm just worried I might be contagious.
明天的总结报告  是的
Inventory. Tomorrow. I'm-Yeah,
我肯定我明天会好一点
I'm sure I'll be feeling better by then.
谢谢  伊纳比先生
Thanks, Mr. Innabe.
真不敢相信你竟然撒谎
I cannot believe you just did that.
我确实咳嗽了
I really do have a cough.
这么说你没说谎喽
Oh. So you weren't lying.
你宁愿乖乖躺在床上喝鸡汤
You'd be curled up in bed with a bowl of chicken soup-
即使你床上有个饥渴难耐的姑娘
even if you didn't have a horny girl in your bed?
是啊  因为我确实
Yes. Because I really do- Hey.
-我确实咳嗽  -你还起疹子了
- I really do have a cough. - You also have a little rash.
我们不该接吻吧  会传染
Um, I'm not sure we should be kissing.
没关系  反正我对光吻你也没兴趣
Oh. It's okay. Because I have almost no interest in kissing you.
-很好  -好
- Perfect. - Good.
宝贝
Oh, baby.
布兰登
Oh, Brandon.
Brandon.
我知道我超棒  快起来啦
I know I'm good, but come on.
布兰登
Brandon?
布兰登  布兰登  布兰登
Brandon. Brandon. Brandon.
布兰登  布兰登
Brandon.! Brandon.!
请空闲的护士到外科门诊
Any additional R.N. to surgical.
你为什么要我去给他看病
Why do you want me to treat this guy?
血压对静脉推注没有反应
Blood pressure's not responding to I.V. fluids.
不  我没问你打算怎么骗我上钩去治他
No, no. I didn't ask how you plan to con me into treating him.
我是问为什么是你  想要我给他治病
I asked you why you want me to treat him.
我动了恻隐之心  我真可悲啊
He's sick. I care. I'm pathetic.
全世界生病的人多了去了  为什么偏偏治他
There are about a billion sick people on the planet. Why this one?
因为他在我们的急诊室里
Because this one's in our emergency room.
所以是就近原则喽
Ah, so it's a proximity issue.
要是有人在三层的楼梯间病倒了
If somebody was sick in the third-floor stairwell,
根据就近原则我该先给他看病
that's who'd we be talking about.
是的  我去楼梯间看过了  没人
Yes. I checked the stairwell. It's clear.
好吧  那就急诊室的这位吧
Okay, then. Emergency room guy it is.
-等等  这次怎么这么容易  -你懂的
- Wait. Why was that so easy? - You know why.
-因为血压对静脉推注没反应吗  -是啊
- Blood pressure's not responding to I.V. fluids? - Yeah.
这太诡异了
That's just weird.
和某电视台一样  血细胞计数没看点
C.B.C. was unremarkable.
同学们  鉴别诊断  她什么病
So, people, differential diagnosis. What's wrong with her?
-是他  -他  她  有关系吗
- Him. - Him. Her. Does it matter?
有人觉得是睾丸问题吗  没有吧
Does anyone think it's a testicular problem? No.
奇斯
So, Chase?
-耶尔森氏菌感染  -不  那不会咳嗽或出疹
- Yersinia infection? - No. You wouldn't get the rash or cough.
是不是关节炎  并发脉管炎导致神经损伤
What about arthritis? Accompanying vasculitis causes nerve damage-
不  那不会导致血压问题  过敏症吗
No. It wouldn't cause the blood pressure problems. Allergy?
那孩子有腹痛
The kid's got abdominal pain.
-可能是良性肿瘤  -不  那不会出现
- Maybe carcinoid? - No. But then you wouldn't get the-
福曼  你要是想把不符合的疾病全列出来
Foreman, if you're going to list all the things it's not,
按字母顺序来会比较快
it might be quicker to do it alphabetically.
来看看  犁头霉属  很好
Let's see, now. "Absidia." Excellent.
以上症状都不包括
Doesn't account for any of the symptoms.
-没有疾病包括全部这些症状  -太好了
- No condition accounts for all these symptoms. - Oh, good.
我还以为他生病了呢
Because I thought maybe he was sick.
现在看来  他健康的很
But, apparently, he's not.
谁自愿去帮他办理出院手续
Who wants to do up the discharge papers?
好吧  除非我们控制住血压
Okay. Unless we control the blood pressure,
不然在我们得出结论之前
he's gonna start circling the drain before we can
他就生命垂危了
figure out what's wrong with him.
按败血症来治疗  用广谱抗生素
Treat him for sepsis, broad-spectrum antibiotics,
做一个皮质醇过量测试和心脏超音波
and I want a cort-stim test and an echocardiogram.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
皮质醇过量测试可以显示
The Cort-stim test will tell us
你的脑垂体和肾上腺是否正常
if your pituitary and adrenal glands are working properly.
他的腺体  那什么意思
His glands? What does that mean?
我们在根据得出的一些理论研究病情
We have a few theories we're working on.
-意思是说你不知道什么病  -敏蒂
- You mean you don't know. - Mindy.
如果他们知道的话就不会给你做测试
I'm just saying, if they knew they wouldn't be testing you,
而是治疗你
they'd be treating you.
是啊  可过程就是这样
Yeah, well, that's the way it works.
我们先诊断出病因  然后对症下药
First we find out what it is, then we get you better.
-你迟到了半小时  -手头病例太多了
- You're half an hour late. - Busy caseload.
就一个病例算不上多
One case is not a load.
今天的棉棒够用吗
So how are we doing on cotton swabs today?
如果不够的话  我可以跑回家去
If there's an acute shortage, I could run home-
-看来你"跑"不了  -很好
- No, you couldn't. - Nice.
患者以及其亲朋好友  你们好
Hello, sick people and their loved ones.
为了节省时间  还有避免大量无聊的闲谈
In the interest of saving time and avoiding a lot of boring chitchat later,
我是格利高里·豪斯医生
I'm Dr.Gregory House.
你们可以叫我格雷戈
You can call me Greg.
我是今早在门诊出诊的三个医生之一
I'm one of three doctors staffing this clinic this morning.
简洁  可爱  拿个病例走人
Short. Sweet. Grab a file.
这位就是总能温暖人心的丽莎·卡迪医生
This ray of sunshine is Dr.Lisa Cuddy.
卡迪医生是这间医院的院长
Dr.Cuddy runs this whole hospital,
所以很不幸  她没时间给你们看病
so, unfortunately, she's much too busy to deal with you.
我是个经过认证的诊断师
I am a board-certified diagnostician,
专业是传染病学和肾脏学
with a double specialty of infectious disease and nephrology.
我也是整个门诊部门目前值班的医生中
I'm also the only doctor currently employed at this clinic
唯一一个被逼出诊的
who is forced to be here against his will.
这是实话  对吧  不过别担心
That is true, isn't it? But not to worry.
对你们大多数人的病情来说
Because for most of you,
这工作简单到猴子拿瓶布洛芬就能解决了
this job could be done by a monkey with a bottle of Motrin.
说到这儿  如果你是特别烦人的病人
Speaking of which, if you're particularly annoying,
你会看到我吃这个东西
you may see me reach for this.
这是维科丁  是我的  你们吃不到
This is Vicodin. It's mine. You can't have any.
我没有什么疼痛处理障碍  我就是疼而已
And, no, I do not have a pain management problem. I have a pain problem.
谁知道呢  也许我错了
But who knows? Maybe I'm wrong.
也许我浑浑噩噩的所以分不清了
Maybe I'm too stoned to tell.
那好  谁要我看病
So, who wants me?
谁宁愿等另外那两个医生来
And who would rather wait for one of the other two guys?
很好  如果你们改变主意
Okay. Well, I'll be in exam room one
去1号门诊室找我
if you change your mind.
乔迪·马修斯
Jodi Matthews?
请和豪斯医生去1号门诊室
Please accompany Dr.House to Exam Room One.
奇斯医生
Dr.Chase.
我认为目前来说
I'm not sure scaring your boyfriend
吓唬你男友对他的病情没有帮助
is the best medicine for him right now.
我知道  我害怕的时候就会变得笨笨的
I know. I get stupid when I'm scared.
那千万别去攀岩
Don't go rock climbing.
我想问问你  他病发之前  我们在做爱
Look, I was wondering. Before this happened, we were having sex.
怎么了  你想知道你是不是被他传染了
What? You're wondering if whatever he has, you might've gotten it?
没事的  我们做了全面的性传播疾病检测
It-It's unlikely. We ran a complete S.T.D. panel, so-
不是  我想知道这是不是因我而起
No. I'm wondering if maybe I did this to him.
我当时有点粗暴
I was kind of rough.
-之前是黄色的  -之前
- It was yellow. - It was?
-现在不是了  -那真遗憾
- It's not anymore. - Well, that's a shame.
我想这么说你不太懂  所以我带了这个来
I thought that might be a problem, so I brought you this.
你的黏液是  浅金黄色
Your mucus was "pale goldenrod."
-上周是这情况  严重吗  -非常之严重
- Last week, yes. Should I be worried? - Oh, yes. Very.
是吗  我觉得现在已经没事了
Really? I thought it was okay now.
可你来医院了  怎么回事
And yet, here you are. What happened?
医护人员花了一周来回复你的急救电话吗
Paramedics took a week to respond to your 911 call?
你不算是个友善的医生  对吧
You're not a very nice doctor, are you?
而你呢  成事不足败事有余
And you are very bad at whatever it is you do.
-你根本不认识我  -我知道你要被炒了
- You don't even know me. - I know you're gonna get fired.
所以你才买了新眼镜
That's why you got the new glasses.
而且做了牙齿漂白
That's why your teeth are sparkly white.
失业之前你在最大限度地利用医疗保险
You're getting the most of your health insurance while you still can.
可能是我辞职呢
I might be quitting.
如果是你辞职  一周之前你就会注意到
If you were quitting, you'd have known that last week
你的鼻涕是浅金黄色  你要被炒了
when your snot was still pale goldenrod. You're getting fired.
我只是讨厌被呼来唤去的
I just don't like being told what to do.
过几天我可以给你安排做一个全身检查
I can get you in for a full body scan later this week.
谢了
Thanks.
肯定是病毒  我们应该做凝胶和滴度的检验
It's got to be viral. We should start running gels and titers.
也许我们该研究一下他女朋友的理论
Maybe we should look into the girlfriend's theory.
她觉得是她把他"做"出毛病的
She thinks she rode him to death.
你怎么说的
What'd you tell her?
我说一个22岁的男性不会死于性爱
I told her 22-year-old men don't die of sex.
-你问她什么了  -你什么意思
- What'd you ask her? - What do you mean?
我希望你有好好了解一下具体情况
I mean, I hope you got some specifics on exactly what was going on.
如果那女孩觉得男性会死于性爱
If the girl thinks it could kill you,
那你绝对有备案的必要
it's worth knowing about.
那你曾经"杀"过人吗
Have you ever taken a life?
我们得停止使用抗生素了
We should stop the antibiotics.
现在断定它们不起作用为时过早
It's too soon to say they're not having an effect.
已经起作用了
They're having an effect.
他血压急降  肺部有积液
His B.P.'s falling fast. There's fluid filling his lungs.
他的肌氨酸酐在上升
His creatinine is rising.
他的肾功能正在衰竭
His kidneys are shutting down.
我们的治疗没有让他好转  是要他的命
Our treatment isn't making him better. It's killing him.
这么说  我们有6个毫无意义的症状
So, we had six symptoms that didn't add up to anything.
现在出现了第7个  有人激动不
Now we got seven. Who's excited?
我认为它没有使问题复杂化
I don't think it complicates things.
肾衰竭是由抗生素引起的
The kidney failure was caused by the antibiotics.
-可能  -通常来说  低血压
- Maybe. - Typically, low blood pressure
和腹痛说明是感染
and abdominal pain means an infection.
腹腔感染导致败血症  低血压
An abdominal infection causes sepsis, low blood pressure.
不过我们已经测试过腹腔感染
Except we checked for abdominal infections.
我知道  不过如果顺序颠倒一下呢
I know. But what if it's the other way around?
如果是低血压造成腹痛呢
What if the low blood pressure's causing the abdominal pain?
病毒性心脏感染
Viral heart infection.
肠道得不到足够血液  导致了腹部疼痛
The intestines aren't getting enough blood, and the result is belly pain.
我知道这套说法站不住脚
I know it's not the standard presentation.
这只有千万分之一的可能性
It's a 10 million-to-1 shot.
所以才要我们来解决
I thought that's what we dealt with here.
这能解释心肌病  疼痛  低血压和发烧
It explains the cardiomyopathy, the pain, the low B.P., the fever.
你真的读那本书了  不错啊
You read the book. Impressive.
这理论荒唐且冒险  解释了所有症状
It's a ludicrously long shot that explains every one of those symptoms
除了咳嗽和皮疹
except for the cough and the rash.
咱们是不是该擦掉那两个
Should we just erase those?
任何东西都能引起皮疹
Well, anything can cause a rash.
好吧  心脏传染病
Okay. Cardiac infection.
卡梅隆  你认为是过敏症
Cameron, you thought allergy.
奇斯  你怎么想的来着  良性肿瘤
Chase, what was it you thought? Carcinoid?
还有甲状腺机能减退
Then there's hypothyroidism.
可能是寄生虫
Could be parasites.
最后是鼻窦感染
Finally, sinus infection.
你要是打算标上所有可能的  颜色不够
If you're gonna list all the things it can be, you're gonna need more colors.
卡梅隆是对的
Cameron was right.
没有任何一种情况可以解释全部症状
No condition explains all these symptoms.
但是橙色和绿色一起  涵盖全部
But orange and green covers everything.
橙色和绿色吗
Orange and green?
两种疾病同时存在吗
Two conditions contracted simultaneously?
奥坎简化律  最简单的解释是最好的
Occam's Razor. The simplest explanation is always the best.
你觉得一个比两个简单
And you think one is simpler than two?
相当确定
Pretty sure it is, yeah.
那小孩出生来说
Baby shows up.
奇斯说是两个人交换体液的结果
Chase tells you that two people exchanged fluids to create this being.
我说是仙鹤把小孩扔到尿布里的
I tell you that one stork dropped the little tyke off in a diaper.
你相信哪一个
Are you gonna go with the two or the one?
-你强词夺理  -你的领带难看
- I think your argument is specious. - I think your tie is ugly.
为什么认为一个比两个简单
Why is one simpler than two?
更低等  更单一  就更简单吗
It's lower, lonelier. Is it simpler?
任何一个病症都是约千分之一的概率
Each one of these conditions is about a thousand-to-one shot.
意味着任何两个同时发生的概率是十万分之一
That means that any two of them happening at the same time is a million-to-one shot.
奇斯提出的心脏感染概率是百万分之一
Chase says the cardiac infection is a 10 million-to-1 shot,
所以我的提议比你们的好十倍
which makes my idea 10 times better than yours.
找个计算器  好好算算
Get a calculator. Run the numbers.
-我们会做检查  -检查太耗时间
- We'll run the tests. - Tests take time.
治疗更快  给他用优立新针对鼻窦感染
Treatment's quicker. Start the kid on Unasyn for the sinus infection,
-橙色是什么来着  -甲状腺机能衰退
- and... what was orange? - Hypothyroidism.
我叔叔也有甲状腺机能衰退
My uncle has hypothyroidism.
不太一样
Not like this.
静注左甲状腺素是合成甲状腺药物
Intravenous Levothyroxin is an artificial thyroid medication
针对此症
that should take care of it.
同时  护士会开始用优立新
Also, the nurses are going to start you on Unasyn.
是一种更有针对性的抗生素
It's a more targeted antibiotic.
-针对鼻窦感染吗  -是
- For the sinus infection? - Yes.
-两者完全不同  -很倒霉吧
- And the other stuff is for something else entirely. - Bad luck, huh?
别担心  他很快就能继续干活了
Don't worry. He should be back to ditching work in no time.
布兰登
Brandon?
妈妈
Hey, Mom.
我们是他的父母  他怎样了
We're his parents. How's he doing?
布兰登是
Um, Brandon is-
妈  爸  这是敏蒂
Uh, Mom. Dad This is Mindy.
我原打算圣诞节带她回家  我们订婚了
I was gonna bring her home for Christmas. Um, we're engaged.
霍尔医生请到术后特别病房  霍尔医生
Dr. Hall to the recovery room. Dr. Hall-
你和家属说了豪斯的理论吗
Did you tell the family House's theory?
两种罕见病症极为巧合的同时发生
Two odd conditions striking completely coincidentally at the exact same time?
-我可没这么说  -他们同意治疗吗
- I didn't phrase it quite that way. - They agree to treatment?
当然同意了  我们是医生
Of course they did. We're doctors.
我们说什么他们都相信
They believe whatever we tell them.
这就是我们的工作  豪斯的木偶吗
So, is that our job? House's puppets?
他冒出个疯狂的想法  我们却置若罔闻吗
He comes up with an insane idea, we get to pretend it's not?
他的疯狂想法通常是对的
His insane ideas are usually right.
我们在这里足够长时间
We've been here long enough to-
足够长时间患上斯德哥尔摩综合征[人质情节]
We've been here long enough to have Stockholm syndrome.
什么  就因为我们不讨厌他吗
What, because we don't hate him?
他能跳出框框思考  就是恶人了吗
He thinks outside the box. Is that so evil?
他根本不知道框子在哪里
He has no idea where the box is.
要是你们觉得他是对的  回家吧
If you guys think he's right, go home.
放松  等着病人好转
Relax. Just wait for the kid to get all better.
我去化验室  检查病毒感染
I'm going to the lab to test for viral infections.
B型柯萨奇病毒检测呈阴性
Negative for Coxsackie "B" virus.
排除7个  还有5000多个
Seven down, about 5,000 to go.
你真的以为靠凝胶实验
You really think we're gonna
加上我们随意的猜测
come up with your mystery virus just by running gels
就能找到你的神秘病毒
till we guess it right?
不  我觉得  站着看别人干活就可以
No. I think we're gonna do it by standing around watching other people work.
我在等EB病毒检测结果
I'm waiting for the Epstein-Barr virus.
-她很古怪  不是吗  -不是好主意
- She's weird, isn't she? - Bad idea.
-什么  -不是好主意  你们是同事
- What? - Bad idea. You work with her.
我说什么了
What did I say?
古怪是黑人对性感的委婉说法吗
Is weird some new ghetto euphemism for sexy,
就像坏是好  漂亮是好
like bad is good and phat is good?
-那么好又指什么  -黑人委婉说法
- Then what the hell does "good" mean? - "Ghetto euphemism"?
你不觉得她很性感吗
You don't think she's hot?
不
No.
明智  这个明智是委婉说法
Wow. Then you're brilliant. And I am using "brilliant" as a euphemism.
显然  她很性感  你不是就美学角度讨论
Obviously, the girl is hot. Y-You're not talking about her aesthetics.
你在说我想和她上床  我不想
You're talking about if I want to jump her. I don't.
明智
Brilliant.
你的EB病毒检测好了
Your Epstein-Barr is ready.
-你在干吗  -第四关
- What are you doing? - Level four.
不  我是说
No, no. I mean
我知道你什么意思  我们等着
I know what you meant. We're waiting.
-我喉咙痛  -那是你说的
- My throat hurts. - So you said.
我们等了多久了
How long are we waiting?
比两分钟前你问的时候少了两分钟
Two minutes less than when you asked me two minutes ago.
-你好  -你好  我是卡迪医生
- Hi. - Hi. I'm Dr. Cuddy.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
卡迪医生  多谢前来会诊
Dr. Cuddy, thanks for the consult.
他的喉咙有些不适
His throat seems to have some condition.
-说"啊"  -啊
- Say "Ah." - Ah.
他喉咙痛
He has a sore throat.
当然  是  我怎么就没
Of course. Yes, why didn't l-
我是说  因为他说疼
I mean, because he said that it hurt,
我应该推断是痛的
and I should have deduced that meant it was sore.
我在开董事会议
I was in a board meeting.
病人优先  不是吗
Patients come first, right?
止咳糖疗效仍有疑问  就不打算开药是吗
Wouldn't want to prescribe a lozenge if there's any doubt about its efficacy, huh?
你曾问我为何我总认为自己是对的
You once asked me why I think I'm always right,
我意识到  你是对的
and I realized that you're right.
至少我认为你对
At least, I think you're right.
我并不真的知道  怎么能知道呢
I don't really know, how do I?
-我在这里呢  -回家  喝点热茶
- Hey. I'm here. - Go home. Drink some hot tea.
出色的会诊
Excellent counsel.
细小病毒B-19阴性
Negative on parvovirus B-19.
-了不起啊  -多谢  天生跑胶的料
- I'm impressed. - Thank you. I was born to run gels.
-我说奇斯呢  -奇斯怎么了
- I meant about Chase. - What about Chase?
这个人对你的外貌没有兴趣
Well, the man has no physical interest in you.
绝对的同事关系
He has a completely professional relationship with you,
尊重你  如同对同事和医生
respects you as a colleague and a doctor.
还有  看着你  满脑袋想的是做爱
And yet, he can't look at you without thinking sex.
就因为我问什么样的性爱能害死人吗
Because I asked what kind of sex could kill you?
你俩的关系  现在你说了算
You now have total control over your relationship with him.
女性必须占据主导
So, a woman can't express her interest in sex
才能表示对性的兴趣吗
without it being some professional power play?
不  但是如果回想下你所说  所做的
No. If you look the way you do and you say what you said,
当心这样做对一个男人产生的影响
you have to be aware of the effect that it's going to have on men.
男人总也长不大
Men should grow up.
对  狗改不了吃屎
Yeah, and dogs should stop licking themselves.
-不会发生的  -出什么事了
- It's not gonna happen. - What's going on?
-对了  你在这里干嘛  -找你们
- Yeah, what are you doing here? - Looking for you guys.
为什么不呼我们
Why didn't you page us?
因为我知道你们在这里
'Cause I knew you'd be here.
-谁告诉他的  -没人
- Who told him? - No one.
料到你们想要证明我疯狂的两病同发理论是错的
I assume you're trying to prove my crazy, two-illness theory wrong,
所以  显然  你们会在化验室
so, obviously, you're gonna be in the lab.
-尿沉渣检验好了吗  -还没
- You spin the urine? - Not yet.
做完了通知我
Talk to me when you have.
发现什么了
What'd you find out?
肾衰  急性间质性肾炎
Kidney failure. It's acute interstitial nephritis.
我在想这重要吗
I wonder if that's significant.
那就表示抗生素并非肾衰诱因
It means the antibiotics didn't cause the kidney failure.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
要是你们没有忙着挑我的刺
If you guys hadn't been so busy trying to prove me wrong,
就会有空观察可怜的男孩
you might've checked in on the poor kid.
你看过病人了吗
You visited a patient?
我在他床边坐了一个早上
I was sitting by his bed all morning,
让他知道还有人关心他
just so he'd know someone was there for him.
我看过他了  好多了
I looked in on him. He's much better.
因此  治疗起效了
Ergo, the treatment's working.
因此  我对  你们错
Ergo, me right, you wrong.
我为男孩高兴
Hey, I'm glad for the kid.
装模作样的确是你的魅力所在
That smugness of yours really is an attractive quality.
谢谢
Thank you.
要不我就去把头发染了
It was either that or get my hair highlighted.
装模作样保持起来要容易得多
Smugness is easier to maintain.
我明白你不相信蜂蜜抓苍蝇的方法
I get that you're not a big believer in the "catching flies with honey" approach,
但你真的相信嘲弄法能抓一罐子吗
but do you honestly think you'll collect a jarful by cleverly taunting them?
苍蝇  不行  医生  一定
Flies, no. Doctors, sure.
要是我和福曼说
If I'd said to Foreman,
"尝试的好  猜得不错
"Nice try. Great guess,
但是对不起  不对"
but sorry, not this time,"
你觉得他现在会在干嘛
what do you think he'd be doing right now?
我想他回家时不会觉得自己一无是处
I think he'd go home not feeling like a piece of crap.
没错
Exactly.
你想让他觉得自己一无是处吗
You want him to feel like a piece of crap?
不  我不想让他回家
No. I don't want him going home.
福曼医生
Dr. Foreman.
-还是咳嗽吗  -但感觉好多了
- Still have the cough. - I'm feeling a lot better though.
他的烧退了  疹子也退了
His fever is gone. His rash is going away.
-知道了  -一切都好吗
- I see. - Is everything okay?
就是预约几个检查  没有什么可担心的
Just ordering some tests. Absolutely nothing to worry about.
还要多久
How much longer?
9点半  我想我呼她的时候  她在8号洞
9:30. I figure she was on the eighth hole when I paged her.
大概能玩半个小时
You probably got another half hour.
我检测了促甲状腺激素  三碘甲状腺素
I ran a T.S.H., T3
甲状腺素  不是甲状腺机能减退
and T4. The patient's negative for hypothyroidism.
说的不是你
I'm not talking about you.
事实是  他在好转
The fact that he's getting better would
说明检测结果不可靠
indicate the unreliability of the tests.
如果我是对的  是病毒感染
If I'm right and it's a viral infection,
下面两种情况必有其一
one of two things always happen:
病人死亡  或病人免疫系统抗击感染
The patient dies, or the patient's immune system fights off the invader.
她怎么回事
What's with her?
跑了6英里后  她腿疼
Her leg hurts after running six miles.
谁知道呢  什么都有可能
Who knows? Could be anything.
他在好转并不证明你是对的
He's getting better. That doesn't prove you're right.
仅证明他在好转
That just proves he's getting better.
不是两病同发  不可能是两病同发
It-It's not two illnesses. It can't be two illnesses.
你在这里工作  我太高兴了
I am so glad you work here.
如果我是对的  你开的抗生素
If I'm right, the antibiotics you prescribed...
会阻断肝肾  抑止抵抗病毒的能力
could box his kidneys and liver, impeding his ability to fight off the virus.
-会害死他的  -这的确值得考虑
- It could kill him. - Well, that certainly would be a concern.
赌50元吗
Fifty bucks?
别走神  太空猴子会打败你的
Don't look away. The space monkeys will be all over you.
你要那病人的健康打赌
You wanna bet on the patient's health?
你认为不吉利吗
You think that's bad luck?
你认为上帝会因我们的无动于衷而惩罚他吗
You think that God will smite him because of our insensitivity?
要是这样  白送你50块
Well, if God does, you make a quick 50.
-噢  -检查他的白细胞计数
- Oh. - Go check his white blood count.
若如你想的是病毒感染  会显著升高
If he's fighting off a virus like you think, it'll be way up.
卡迪说你要求会诊  什么事  我忙呢
Hey. Cuddy said you needed a consult. What's up? I'm busy.
-我就是一时嘴快  -你什么也没说
- I was just being glib. - You haven't said anything.
不  之前  我说布兰登女友
No. Before, when I was talking about Brandon's girlfriend
认为做爱能害死人的时候
thinking sex could kill you.
我就是开玩笑  因为我不是很自在
I was just making a joke because I was uncomfortable.
我连你说过什么都不记得了
Oh, I don't even remember what you said.
性让我心神不安
I'm uncomfortable about sex.
-我们没有必要讨论这个  -性能害死你
- Well, we don't have to talk about this. - Sex could kill you.
你知道在做爱时人体会发生什么变化吗
Do you know what the human body goes through when you have sex?
瞳孔放大  动脉收缩
Pupils dilate. Arteries constrict.
体温上升  心跳加速  血压猛涨
Core temperature rises, heart races, blood pressure skyrockets.
呼吸短浅而急促
Respiration becomes rapid and shallow.
大脑肆意地
The brain fires bursts of
放射电脉冲
electrical impulses from nowhere to nowhere.
各腺体排放分泌物
Secretions spit out of every gland,
肌肉的收缩程度
and the muscles tense and spasm
相当于你在举起你体重三倍的重物
Like you're lifting three times your body weight.
它就是暴力  丑陋与肮脏的混合体
It's violent, it's ugly, and it's messy.
如果上帝没有把性变得难以置信地有趣
and if god hadn't made it unbelievably fun,
那么人类早已灭绝了
the human race would've died out eons ago.
男人只有一次性高潮是很幸运的事情
Men are lucky they can only have one orgasm.
你知道女人会有长达一小时的性高潮吗
You know that women can have an hour-long orgasm?
嘿  福曼  怎么了
Hey, Foreman. What's up?
-嘿  福曼  -嗨
- Hey, Foreman. - Hey.
白血球数量不高  是吧
White cell count isn't up, is it?
是的  我们都错了
No. We were both wrong.
白血球数量极低  而且还在下降
White cell count is down- way down-and dropping.
他的免疫系统衰竭了  我们要把他带到无菌室
His immune system is shot. We need to get him into a clean room.
你还能走吗  布兰登
Can you walk, Brandon?
嗯  勉强可以吧
Yeah. A little.
很好  因为我们不能把轮椅带进去  谢谢了
Okay. 'Cause we'll need to leave the chair outside. Thank you.
艾普尔在哪里  艾普尔
Where's April? April?
麻烦把轮椅拿出去  谢谢了
Can you take that chair, please? Thank you.
没问题  罗伯特
Yes, Robert.
我要把你的口罩和长袍脱下
I'll need to take your, um- your mask and your robe too.
塞住你的耳朵的吧  会很吵的
You might wanna block your ears for this, it's quite loud.
某些东西使他的免疫减弱了
Something's made him immuno-compromised.
他的白血球含量很低
His white blood cell count is down,
就是说他的身体不能抵抗感染
which means his body can't fight off infections.
如果他稍有生病  他就会死了
If he gets sick, he'll die.
稍有生病  什么样的病
Sick? How sick?
如果他感冒了  他就会死
If he gets a cold, he'll die.
好了  我会把针穿进你的髋骨取出一些骨髓
Okay. I'm gonna push the needle into your hip bone and take some of the marrow.
这也没多疼啊
That's not so bad.
这只是麻醉而已
That was just the anesthetic.
真正的活组织检查针头  有点大了
The core biopsy needle, it's a bit bigger.
兄弟  深呼吸吧  这将是非一般的疼
Hey, man. Take a deep breath. This-this is gonna hurt... A lot.
你的骨髓制造血细胞
Your marrow makes the blood cells.
我们在显微镜下观察一下
We take a peek at it under a microscope,
也许就会发现病毒感染
and maybe we find a viral infection.
也可能会发现纤维变性
Maybe we find some fibrosis.
反正是可以解释你血细胞数量那么低的东西
Something to explain why your blood count is so low.
搞定了
There we go.
离答案又近了一步了
One step closer to an answer.
如果你找不到的话
If you don't find one,
我也不能一直在无菌室里待着
I can't stay here forever.
-病人可能会死  -肌肉拉伤那个吗
- The patient could've died. - The one with the pulled muscle?
还有很多种疾病可以出现这个症状
Those symptoms are consistent with a dozen other conditions.
我有权参加会诊啊
I'm entitled to a consult.
你逃不掉门诊任务的
You are not getting out of clinic duty.
拜托  你还有一堆白痴医生能很热情
Come on. You got a hundred other idiot doctors in this building who go...
富有同情心  去给别人拿出鼻子里的玩具车
warm and fuzzy every time they pull a toy car out of a nose,
你根本不用我在这里
you don't need me here.
我是不需要
No, I don't.
但是和他人一起工作能让你进步
But working with people actually makes you a better doctor.
我什么时候报名上这堂课了
When did I sign up for that course?
我什么时候让你觉得我在意了
When did I give you the impression that I care?
在门诊工作显然会慢慢变得更有同情心
Working in this clinic obviously instills a deep sense of compassion.
我有你家的电话号码的吧
I've got your home number, right?
就怕凌晨3点会有突发事件
In case anything comes up at 3:00 in the morning.
没有用的  知道为什么吗
It's not gonna work. You know why?
因为这挺好玩的
Because this is fun.
你想尽办法让我悲惨
You think of something to make me miserable.
我也想尽办法让你悲惨
I think of something to make you miserable.
这是个游戏  我会赢的
It's a game, and I'm gonna win
我已经有个好的开端了  你已经很悲惨了
Because I got a head start. You are already miserable.
这很重要吗
Is this important?
-不  -很好
- Uh, no. - Good.
-你和她怎么了  -别问了
- What's with you and her? - Don't.
你喜欢她的是吧  唯一可以让你...
You have a thing for her? The only people who can get to you-
不  恨与爱不只有一线之隔
No. There is not a thin line between love and hate.
事实上  爱与恨之间是有一道长城
There is, in fact, a great wall of china,
每隔20尺还有武装的哨兵
with armed sentries posted every 20 feet between love and hate.
-36片维科丁  -病人是谁
- Thirty-six vicodin. - Who's the patient?
-我  -你不能
-I am. - You can't-
-威尔森医生是处方医师  -是的
- Dr. Wilson is the prescribing physician. - Yeah.
你为了拿到你想要的会撒谎  欺骗和偷窃
You will lie, cheat and steal to get what you want,
但是你不会拍马屁
but you're incapable of kissing a little ass?
我们都有不足之处
We all have our limitations.
豪斯  你拿错药了  帮我个忙
House? Wrong bottle. Do me a favor.
吃一片药  等个5分钟
Take one of these, wait five minutes
让它发挥药性  然后去找卡迪拍拍马屁
for it to kick in, then find Cuddy and kiss her ass.
那孩子最先的症状是什么
What was the kid's first symptom?
你整理的病历  他的800个症状
You did the history. Of his 800 symptoms,
哪个是第一个
which one hit him first?
咳嗽
Uh, the cough.
痛风
Gout.
-我们在讨论布兰登吗  -痛风吗
- Are we talking about Brandon? - Gout?
关节里有尿酸结晶吗
Uric acid crystals in the joints?
症状是疼痛  肿胀  发红
The symptoms are pain, swelling, redness,
四肢强直  我在白板上一个都看不到啊
stiffness. Not one of which do I see on that board.
因为他没有得痛风
Because he doesn't have gout.
每一天  细胞都会死
Every day, cells die.
我们还活着是因为
We survive because the
活细胞分裂取代死掉的细胞
remaining cells divide and replace the losses.
秋水仙素  治疗痛风的药物
The colchicine, a gout medicine,
阻挡了有丝分裂和停止了细胞分裂
blocks mitosis and stops cell division,
会引起腹部的疼痛  皮疹
which will result in abdominal pain, rash,
恶心  发烧  肾衰竭  低血压
nausea, fever, kidney failure, low blood pressure...
还会在骨髓里捣乱
and will also mess with the bone marrow.
但是他没有痛风  为什么他会吃痛风药
But he doesn't have gout. Why would he have gout medication?
因为你们是正确的
Because you guys were right.
他没有同时出现两个状况
He didn't have two conditions at the exact same time.
首先  他咳嗽
First, he got a cough.
又因为他是个白痴  他去找医生了
And because he's an idiot, he went to a doctor.
为了不愧对收他的两百美金
In order to justify charging $200,
那医生就觉得他应该做些什么
that doctor felt he should actually do something.
他写了一个处方
Oops. He wrote a prescription.
每年有7千人死于药房的错误
Seven thousand people die each year from pharmacy screwups.
不亚于死于医生的出错
Not nearly as many as die from doctor screwups,
但仍然  不会影响医生们的晋升
But still, not something they use in their promotional materials.
药剂师没给他咳嗽药反而给他痛风药
The pharmacist gave him gout medicine instead of cough medicine.
唯一不会有的一个作用就是
And the only thing it wouldn't do,
不会治好他的咳嗽
it would do absolutely nothing to relieve his cough.
奥坎简化律
Occam's razor-
最简单的解释
The simplest explanation
经常就是什么人出错了
is almost always that somebody screwed up.
但当他住进来我们医院的时候
But once he checked into this hospital,
他就完全在我们控制之下了
he was completely in our control.
我们提供的食物  药物  一切东西
Our food, our pills, our everything.
所以即使你是对的  断绝痛风药之后
So even if you're right, no more gout medication.
要么他的病情持续恶化
He'd either continue to deteriorate,
要么就好了
or he would've gotten better.
但是他是先转好  然后再恶化的
But he got better, and then he got worse.
这不对头啊  没有道理啊
It doesn't fit. It doesn't make sense.
好吧  两个人出错了
Okay. Two people screwed up.
没有一个人出错那么简单  但是
Not as simple as one, but-
-他在休息呢  -我是豪斯医生
- He's resting. He's - I'm Dr. House.
是你们孩子的医生
I'm your son's physician.
哦  是那个我们还没有见过的医生
Oh. You're the one we haven't met yet.
也是他没有见过的医生
You're the one he hasn't met.
没有见过病人你怎么治疗病人呢
How can you treat someone without meeting them?
只要不和他说什么废话就很容易
It's easy if you don't give a crap about him.
那是件好事
That's a good thing.
如果感情让你理性行事
If emotions made you act rationally,
那就不会叫做感情了  是吧
well, they wouldn't be called emotions, right?
那就是我们为什么有分工合作的原因
That's why we have this nice division of labor.
你握着他的手  我让他好转
You hold his hand, I get him better.
如果我晚上来守着他
If I start tucking him in at night,
那就对你们不公平了
well, that's not fair to you guys.
而如果你们去写处方
And if you start prescribing medicine,
那就对我不公平了
well, that's not fair to me.
所以  我想知道的是  谁踏进我这半场了
So, what I wanna know is, who stepped on my side of the net?
谁那么过于关心他
Who cared enough to get
笨到又让他吃咳嗽药了
stupid enough to give him his cough medicine?
当我们入住的时候  福曼医生
When we checked in, Dr. Foreman-
星期二  他好转了  星期三  又恶化了
Tuesday, he's getting better. Wednesday, he's getting sick again.
某人让他在星期三的时候吃了咳嗽药
Somebody gave him his cough medicine wednesday.
拜托  没有人会生气的
Come on. Nobody's gonna be mad.
我只是想知道谁试图杀了那小孩
I just wanna know who tried to kill the kid.
-豪斯医生  我们或许  -他喉咙疼
- Dr. House, maybe we should... - His throat was sore.
-呼叫奥克姆医生  他会想听听  -抱歉
- Page Dr. Occam. He's gonna wanna hear about this.  - I'm sorry.
他那时候在咳嗽  我只是想帮他
He was coughing, and I just wanted to help him.
你真可爱
Aren't you a dear.
药呢
Where are the pills?
在他换到那间病房之前他吃掉最后一片了
He took the last of'em before he was switched into that room.
-都吃完了嘛  -那只是咳嗽药
- They're all gone? - It was just cough medicine.
那不是咳嗽药  瓶子在哪
No, it wasn't. Where's the bottle?
我们要知道你到底放了什么药进这瓶子里
We need to know exactly what you put in this bottle.
我们认为是秋水仙素  治疗痛风的药
We think it was colchicine, a gout medication.
如果处方上写的是咳嗽药  我装瓶的就是
If the prescription said cough medicine, that's what I dispensed.
他们不打算追究责任  好吧
The family is prepared to waive liability, all right?
我们只是想知道里面是什么
We just need to know what it was,
-剂量是多少  -就是咳嗽药
- What dosage it was... - It was cough medicine.
再装一次
Refill it.
-他会没事的  -谁知道呢
- He's gonna be okay.  - You don't know that.
布兰登就喜欢你这种性格的人吗
Does Brandon like that quality in you?
你有些消极
You're a little negative.
事情不全是往好的方面发展的
Things don't always work out for the best.
希望它好也没有坏处啊
Doesn't hurt to hope they do.
是的  直到让你认为
No. Not unless that makes you figure you
你可以为所欲为  就像给别人吃咳嗽药
can do whatever you want, like give people cough medicine.
这是咳嗽药
This is cough medication.
这是布兰登应该拿到的药
This is what Brandon was supposed to get.
圆形黄色小药片
They're small, round and yellow.
你可以告诉这个人到底
Can you tell this man what the pills
你孩子的药瓶里装的药是怎样的吗
in your son's medicine bottle actually looked like?
就是像这样的圆形黄色小药片
They were small, round and yellow, exactly like this.
这就是布兰登当时吃的药
Those were the pills that Brandon was taking.
嘿  也许我只是个小小药剂师
Hey, I'm just a pharmacist,
但我认得止咳药什么样  医生
but I know what cough medicine looks like, Doctor.
原本是多么完美  多么美好
It was so perfect. It was beautiful.
美好常常在通往真理的路上诱惑我们
Beauty often seduces us on the road to truth.
而陈腐把我们推入泥沼
And triteness kicks us in the nads.
-如此真实  -你不感到困扰吗
- So true. - This doesn't bother you?
为你的错误吗  我努力走出痛苦
That you were wrong? I try to work through the pain.
我没有错  我说的全部都是事实
I was not wrong. Everything I said was true.
切合病情  一流的诊断
It fit. It was elegant.
这么说  是现实错了吗
So, reality was wrong?
现实几乎总是错的
Reality's almost always wrong.
他吃的止咳药肯定有问题
The cough medicine did something.
加重了病情
Aggravated the condition.
扩散到全身  一定在他的血液里
It's all over the place. Must be in his blood.
-如果是血液本身呢  -淋巴瘤
- What if it is his blood? - Lymphoma?
除非你有更好的解释
Unless you've got something better.
我们愚蠢地排除了淋巴瘤
We foolishly ruled out lymphoma
因为他的CT扫描没有淋巴结肿大
because his C.T. scan showed no adenopathy,
全血细胞计数正常
C.B.C. Showed a normal differen-smear,
-骨髓也没有...  -别管这些检查了
- bone marrow showed no-- - Screw the tests.
做个剖腹探查  找出是什么在作怪
Do an exploratory laparotomy and find out what's in there.
他没有血压  没有免疫系统  也没有肾
He has no blood pressure, no immune system and no kidneys.
手术会要了他的命
Surgery will kill him.
对  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
我们就继续认为他吃错药好了
Let's stick with the wrong pill theory.
我来给他安排手术时间
I'll schedule him for surgery.
准备好  布兰登
Okay, Brandon,
我们正在用电子导管检视你的心脏
we're running this tube through your heart...
然后进入肺动脉
and into the pulmonary arteries in your lungs.
传感器会给我们提供
The sensors will give us information we need
下午探查手术所需信息
for the exploratory surgery later this afternoon.
-我手指没感觉了  -尽量不要动
- My fingers are numb. - Try not to move.
现在导管到了右心房
We're in the right atrium,
我们正试图截取三尖瓣血流图像
trying to catch the flow through the tricuspid valve.
我认为导管在心房处弯曲了
I think the catheter's curling in the atrium.
了解  现在在右心室
Got it. We're in the R.V. Now.
异位搏动
Ectopy.
-肯定是你刺激到了心壁  -会平稳下来的
- You must've irritated the heart wall. - It'll calm down.
他经不起任何心律失常
He can't tolerate any cardiac arrhythmia.
-拉回去  -他需要手术
- Pull back. - He needs the surgery.
血压下降
Pressure's dropped.
-能听到我们吗  布兰登  -拉上窗帘
- You still with us, Brandon? - Get the curtains.
室颤
V.F.
充电  闪开
Charging. Clear.
窦心律
Sinus rhythm.
有脉搏了
I got a pulse.
是  但今天做不成手术了
Yeah, but no surgery today.
-你好吗  -还行
- How're you doing? - Okay.
很好  我也不错
Great. I'm doing good too.
我今天可以提前一小时下班  知道为啥吗
I get to knock off an hour early today. You know why?
因为我拍了我老板的马屁  用过这招吗
Because I kissed my boss's ass. Do you ever do that?
我想她同意我早下班
I think she just said yes
是因为她想强化我的拍马屁行为
'cause she wants to reinforce that behavior.
希望我多拍拍别人的马屁
Wants me to kiss a lot of other people's ass,
比方说拍你马屁
like she wants me to kiss yours.
给你选择  你会要哪种
What would you want?
在弥留之际握住你的手的医生
A doctor who holds your hand while you die,
还是不理睬你却能让你好转的医生呢
or a doctor who ignores you while you get better?
我猜要是摊上个在你快死的时候
I guess it would particularly suck
对你不理不睬的医生一定相当郁闷
to have a doctor who ignores you while you die.
我还是走吧
I should go.
你以为那玩意儿自己会出来
You think it's gonna come out on its own?
不会是比胃还严重吧
Are we talking bigger than a breadbasket?
因为实际来讲  是会自己跑出来的
Because, actually, it will come out on its own.
东西不大的话没什么问题
Which for small stuff is no problem.
被软绵绵的漂亮东西包裹着  扑通一声
It's wrapped up in a nice, soft package, and plop.
东西大的话  你要拽一拽才能出来
Big stuff, you're gonna rip something,
从医学角度讲
which, speaking medically,
-就比较无趣了  -你怎么知道...
- is when the fun stops. - How did you--
你在这儿半个钟头了
You've been here half an hour,
坐都不坐一下  说明是某个特殊位置
you haven't sat down. That tells me its location.
你到现在还没告诉我是什么
You haven't told me what it is.
说明是个丢人的事
That tells me it's humiliating.
你手臂上有个小鸟纹身
You have a little birdie carved on your arm.
这说明你对丢人有高度忍受能力
That tells me you have a high tolerance for humiliation.
所以我估计不是痔疮
So I figure it's not hemorrhoids.
我行医二十年了  不会被你吓到的
I've been a doctor 20 years. You're not gonna surprise me.
是个MP3
It's an MP3 player.
你是  你是因为它大小正好  形状适合
Is it- Is it because of the size, or the shape,
还是重低音效果好
or is it the pounding bass line?
我们要怎么办
What are we gonna do?
-我打算等  -等什么
- I'm gonna wait. - For what?
好了  三点到了  我走了
Okay. It's 3:00. I'm off.
麻烦告诉卡迪医生
Would you tell Dr. Cuddy
二号检查室有个病人需要她治疗
there's a patient in Exam Room Two needs her attention?
另外美国唱片工业协会希望她查一查非法下载
And the R.I.A.A. wants her to check for illegal downloads.
-布兰登还不能做手术  -行啊
- Brandon's not ready for surgery. - Okay.
让我们等上几个星期
Let's leave it a couple of weeks.
到时候他应该会感觉好些
He should be feeling better by then.
噢  等会儿  时间走哪条道
Oh, wait. Which way does time go?
他术前准备差点不行了
He crashed during prep.
而且他的手指疼
He's also experiencing pain in his fingers.
可能无菌室有虫子飞进去了
Think some bug may have gotten in the clean room.
我们是不是应该加倍
I think we should double
粒细胞集落刺激因子的剂量
his dosage of G-CSF
让他临时增加白血球数量
to temporarily boost his white blood cell count.
手指上的疼痛感  对了
Pain in his fingers. Right.
-又见面了  -他不能...他去哪儿
- Hi again. - He can't-- Where's he going?
嘿  大伙儿好吗
Hey. How you all doing?
有趣的事实
Interesting fact.
每隔七年  就是一个全新的你
Every seven years, it's a whole new you.
鼓舞人心的比喻  对吧
Inspiring metaphor, huh?
-豪斯医生这是无菌室  -是  我看标志了
- Dr. House, this is a clean room. - Yeah. I read the sign.
但是器官不同  细胞繁殖速度也不一样
But cells of different organs reproduce at different rates.
于是乎  每三年你有个新肾
So, you get a new kidney every three years.
每星期有新的胃壁
Get a new stomach lining every week.
这就是为什么秋水仙素中毒引起这些症状
This is why colchicine poisoning causes all these symptoms,
但不是全部同时显现
but not all at once.
但我们去了药房  我们看到药片了
But we went to the pharmacy. We saw the pills.
秋水仙素发挥毒性是有特定顺序的
Colchicine does its damage in a very specific order.
首先
First of all,
会有腹痛  皮疹  发热
there's the pain in the abdomen, the rash, the fever.
这些不就是你起初的症状吗
Isn't that what you got first?
然后肾脏受损  这正是发生在...
Then the kidneys go, which is exactly what happened to--
-布兰登身上  -对
- Brandon. - Right.
接着骨髓出问题  然后神经病变
Then it screws up your bone marrow, and then neuropathy.
手指和脚趾出现刺痛
A painful tingling in the fingers and toes.
再然后你猜会发生什么呢
And what do you suppose happens after that?
头发脱落  告诉你个坏消息...
Hair loss. The bad news is...
-你的宝贝儿子在吸毒  -错  他没有
- your special boy is doing drugs. - No, he's not.
-迷幻药  -不可能
- Ecstasy? - No.
两次  和丹还有麦克一起
Twice with Dan and Mike.
你知不知道那东西用什么合成的
You know what they cut that stuff with?
显然  秋水仙素
Apparently, colchicine.
除非你体内的秋水仙素是通过
Unless you ingested the colchicine
隐形眼镜溶液  护肤霜
through your contact lens solution,
或者其它你不肯说的药物吸收到的
or skin cream or some other drug you're lying about.
我不知道这是怎么发生的  我也不在意
I don't know how it happened. I don't care how it happened.
总之是发生了  给...
It happened. Start, uh-
-布兰登  -可爱的名字
- Brandon. - Lovely name.
给布兰登用
Start Brandon
FAB片断[免疫球蛋白上结合抗原的片段]
on FAB fragments,
再给他几片泰诺[解热镇痛]
and get him some Tylenol
我拔了他头发怪疼的
for the hair I pulled out.
给里面透透气
And get some air in here.
记下这条  我永远不该怀疑自己
Make a note. I should never doubt myself.
我想你会记得的
I think you'll remember. You know,
知道吗  你偶尔出个错不会伤你自尊的
it wouldn't hurt you to be wrong every now and then.
怎么  你不担忧病人的安危吗
What, you don't care about these people?
秋水仙素会妨碍
The colchicine interferes
心肌收缩能力
with the ability of the heart muscle to contract,
使血液回流  血压降低
pumping blood, lowering your blood pressure.
我们给你的抗体
The antibodies we're giving you
可以中和秋水仙素
should neutralize the colchicine,
让你的心脏以正常速率跳动
allowing your heart to beat at its normal rate.
什么时候能知道起作用了
When will you know?
现在已经知道了
We know now.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
周末过足瘾吗
Big weekend?
不是我要药  我的存货充足
It's not for me. I'm fully stocked.
-卡迪要你盘点药房库存  -不是
- Cuddy got you doing inventory? - Nope.
想要解决那孩子的病案
Trying to solve that kid's case.
-痛风药服食过量那个吗  -对啊
- The gout medicine O.D.? - Yeah.
事实是我知道是痛风药过量
The fact that I know it's a gout medicine O.D.
就意味着这个病案已经完结
would indicate the case is already solved.
你这么想就错了
Well, you'd be wrong.
那么另一事实呢  这个孩子现在已经
What about the fact that the kid is now-
用术语来说应该是"痊愈"
I believe the technical term is-- "Not sick"?
你知道市面上
You know how many forms
有多少种形式的秋水仙素吗
of colchicine there are on the market?
-停  -我也不知道  但太多了
- Stop it. - Neither do I. But it's a lot.
药片  粉末  液体  静脉注射
Pills, powders, liquids, I. V. Fluids.
某个地方的一场派对
Somewhere at a party,
他在咖啡里喝到  眼睛看到  耳朵听到
in his coffee, up his nose, in his ear,
这小子有过一些
this kid had some.
这么说你对迷幻药的说法不满意
So you're not happy with your Ecstasy theory?
-他承认用过两次  -人都会说谎
- He said he used it twice. - People lie.
没错  如果你要说谎  那是...
Yeah. If you're gonna lie, it's--
你猜怎么着  我没兴趣听
You know what? I'm not interested.
-不好奇吗  -不  因为我心里满足了
- Not curious? - No. Because I'm well-adjusted.
确实
Right.
-体温正常  -我想雪伦表妹在场
- Temperature's normal. - I want cousin Sharon there.
如果我们邀请雪伦
If we invite Sharon,
我们就得请所有的表亲
we have to invite all the cousins.
那有什么关系  我家这边不需要什么的
So what? My side of the family doesn't need anything.
我觉得
I don't suppose
我不可以吃那些止咳药
I could have some of those cough pills, huh?
-其实药没事的  对吧  -是的
- They're okay, right? - Yes.
-你现在情况很好  -你应该邀请豪斯医生
- You're doing great. - You should invite Dr. House.
-他会来吗  -不会  但他会送份礼物
- Will he come? - No. But he'll send a gift.
我帮你把把关确保是好东西
I'll make sure it's a good one.
这些药片背面有个字母
There's a letter on the back of these pills.
你之前吃的药片上面没有字母
Your old pills didn't have a letter on them?
没有  是圆形黄色的  但没有字母
No. Round and yellow, but no letter.
没事  这些会治好你的咳嗽的
Well, these will help your cough.
-嘿  你想不想去...  -不用了
- Hey, you wanna go get some-- - No.